Theater Arts Department. Publications. 1920-1989.
UCLA Library Special Collections
Theater Arts Department. Publications.
1920-1989
University Archives Record Series 124
UCLA Library Special Collections
0.8 linear ft. (2 boxes)
Record Series 124 contains the publications of UCLA's Theatre Arts Department.
University of California, Los Angeles. Theater Arts Department.
Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
Scope and Content
Record Series 124 contains the publications of UCLA's Theatre Arts Department. Files include season previews, POV, lists of productions, lists of student films, newspaper clippings, reports, and lists of the Hugh O'Brian Annual Acting Awards.
This is an inactive record series; no additional University records are expected to be added.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 3466884
- POV., 1980-1981. (Box 1)
- Documents., 1947-1967. (Box 1)
- Hugh O'Brian Annual Acting Awards., 1966-1986. (Box 1)
- Newspaper Clippings., 1929-1986. (Box 1)
- Productions., 1920-1989. (Box 1)
- Season Previews., 1973-1974; 1985-1986. (Box 1)
- UCLA Extension Theatre Group., 1959-1966. (Box 1)
- UCLA Resident Theatre Company., 1978. (Box 1)
- UCLA Student Films., 1965-1970. (Box 1)
- UCLA Theatre Arts Department., n.d. (Box 1)
- Report of the Southern California Conference of Education Theatre Workers., 1946. (Box 2)
- UCLA Theatre Arts Department Productions., 1940-1969. (Box 2)